Hello to schw reproduce
Mr. Renogu
Mr. Rengoku?
Mr. Rengoku!
I...
I will see my duty fulfilled!
No matter what it takes, no one shall die here!
Flame breathing.
Esoteric art!
Set your heart ablaze.
Mr. Rengoku!
No!
Set your heart ablaze.
Mr. Rengoku?
Thank you.
Mr. Rengoku.
Stop that train, will ya?
And you, snap out of it and get back on your feet!
We all have to train!
You hear me?
Is that so?
Tanjiro said that.
I'm not done with you, coward!
Turn and face me!
Don't forget that the Demon Slayer Corps is always fighting you demons in the dead of night!
Where you have the advantage!
Don't run away, you bastard!
You're a coward!
A coward!
Then our newfound duty is to carry on his will.
Now, it's a resource.
No one was trapped!
You're a coward!
Look wee!
All right!
There is no joy!
We'll be right back.
I may have that boy take over my business one day.
I'd be lying if I said I weren't jealous.
I wish I could trade our useless son for him.
He's a fine young lad, there's no doubt.
That being said, the poor boy suffers from a rare skin disease, so he can't go outside during the day.
Oh dear, I'm so sorry.
I'm hoping we can figure out a way to develop a miracle elixir for him over at my company.
The sooner the better.
Reporting in as you requested, Lord Muzan.
Were you able to find what I asked for?
I looked into it, but came up empty-handed.
I couldn't find the blue spider lily.
There wasn't even a trace of its existence.
And?
I will try to live up to your expectations.
Forgive my unworthy efforts.
But as you ordered, I was able to eliminate one of the Hashira.
Rest easy knowing that much.
It seems like you have the wrong idea about how things work here, Akaza.
I'm curious.
Did you expect praise?
All you did was dispose of a mere cockroach.
A demon beating a human is an underwhelming conclusion.
What I want is for the Demon Slayer core to be wiped out.
Squeeze the life out of every last one of them.
And never let another one enter my line of sight again.
It's hardly a complicated task.
And yet I am still waiting for it to happen.
Now what do you make of that?
You return here boasting of your infantile triumph over a Hashira.
All the while, three other Demon Slayers survived the confrontation.
Why did you not kill them when you had the chance?
And after I made a point of sending you to that location because you happened to be nearby.
Akaza.
Akaza!
You have disappointed me so.
To think you suffered a blow by someone who isn't even a Hashira.
Ah, how far you have fallen, Upper Three.
You're dismissed.
What's all the commotion up here?
Are you alright?
You coward!
Make no mistake.
I'll remember your face.
And when we meet again,
I'm going to save her tearing you limb from limb.
I'm sorry.
I never thought I'd live to see the day
where even Tanjiro couldn't bring himself to smile.
It makes sense, though.
We were powerless compared to Mr. Rengoku.
And even he found himself at death's door.
I don't blame him.
I would break anyone.
I mean, just look at Inosuke.
I didn't even know he could cry.
He must have been so frustrated
that his burning rage turned to helpless tears.
Even so, there's no point in cowering forever.
The strong get back up on their feet time and time again.
I know Mr. Rengoku was that way.
I could hear that in him.
He was a little odd at times,
but his heart was strong and kind.
Tanjiro!
I snagged his bean paste buns.
Let's eat!
Help!
Mr. Tanjiro has gone missing!
Oh no!
Mr. Zenitsu!
I'm so sorry!
Don't worry about it.
I'll be okay.
Eventually.
You look like you just got hit by a train.
Please forgive me, sir.
But Mr. Tanjiro can't be found!
Even worse!
His wounds haven't healed and he's training again!
Maybe Shinobu told him he should be resting in bed!
But he didn't listen and now we don't know what we should do!
So he's training with that stomach wound?
Is he dumb?
Mr. Rengoku's crow.
Thank you.
He's carrying out his master's will by guiding me to his house.
Are you...
Senjuro?
Are you Senjuro?
I take it you know about Mr. Kyojiro?
I'm so sorry.
Before he died, he asked for some messages to be delivered to you and your father.
I've come to pass them on.
From my brother?
Thank you, but I'm already well aware of what happened to him.
What's wrong?
Your face...
It looks as pale as a ghost.
Knock it off!
Whatever message she left means nothing anyway!
Why would he become a swordsman when he had no talent to begin with?
It's no wonder he died!
He's worthless!
He was a fool of a son from the start!
A person's potential is determined the day they're born.
Only a mere handful have any talent.
The rest are just dregs of society.
You're either born a genius or someday killed by one!
It's clear which one Kyojiro was.
He had no future to begin with.
No surprise he got killed.
Give me a break.
The funeral is over, Senjuro.
It's high time you move on with your damn life!
Just a moment.
Don't you think you're being a bit too harsh?
Please show some respect for your son!
And just who the hell are you?
Answer me!
Or get off of my property!
I'm with the Demon Slayer Corps!
You're what?
I get it now.
That means...
You're a sun-breathing user, aren't you?
Am I right?
Sun-breathing?
What do you mean by that?
He's fast!
And knows where no amateur moves!
Father!
Please stop!
Take a good look at his face!
Can't you see he's in pain?
Keep your mouth shut!
Don't you dare lay a hand on him, you monster!
Why are you acting so hostile like this in the first place?
Insulting your own child who lost his life?
And striking your son?
What's the matter with you?
Despicable.
You intend to mock us after everything we've been through!
What makes you say that?
I don't know what you're talking about!
I'm here to help!
A sun-breathing user would never help people like us!
I know all about those earrings of yours!
It was in that book!
Sun-breathing sounds familiar!
Is he talking about Hinokami Kagura?
The sun-breathing technique...
Not only is it the first one ever to be created,
it's the most powerful one as well!
Every technique, no matter how diverse, came from sun-breathing!
Which means all the others are just cheap imitations of sun-breathing!
They can try to copy the original, but they'll never be as powerful!
Fire!
Water!
Wind!
All of them!
What does he mean?
We've always been charcoal burners!
It's in our blood!
Sun-breathing...
Hinokami Kagura...
No...
Never mind all that...
There's something more important...
Don't get cocky just because you're a sun-breathing user!
I can still put you in your place, boy!
How can I feel cocky after all that's happened?
I would give anything at all for strength like that, but I'm burdened by my own weakness!
You bastard!
So shut up!
He's powerful!
Be careful!
How dare you badmouth Mr. Rengoku!
You monster!
Need the former Hashira!
Please, father!
Have mercy!
Why then...
If Hinokami Kagura is a sun-breathing technique...
Then that day...
Why wasn't I strong enough to save him?
Why?
Why couldn't I save him?
I feel like I've made a grave mistake.
Please, sir.
Have some tea.
Oh, thank you very much.
I hope you can forgive me...
For head-butting your father and all.
He's okay, right?
Oh, yeah.
He'll be fine.
I mean, after all...
He's back to getting sake already.
What a relief.
You have my thanks.
Huh?
For standing up to him.
I was too scared to.
Even when he badmouthed my brother like that.
Tell me.
What were my brother's last moments like?
I see.
So he was brave to the end.
Thank you for sharing.
Please, don't thank me.
Instead, forgive me.
I wasn't enough.
There's no need to blame yourself.
It's not your fault.
And he knows that, too.
What you said reminded me of something in a book my father often read.
I'm fairly certain this is it.
Thank you very much.
Let me know if what you're looking for is in those pages.
What?
Look at this.
What happened?
It's ripped to shreds.
I can't read it.
Was it like this when he got it?
Not at all.
That's not even possible.
The Flame Hashira Chronicles are stored with the highest degree of care.
Which means it must have been my father who tore them.
I hope you'll forgive me.
Don't worry.
It's not like it's your fault, Senjiro.
So don't beat yourself up over it.
But you traveled all this way for it, didn't you?
The secrets of sun breathing.
I thought for sure I had the answers for you.
But I was no help.
You helped plenty.
This confirmed what I thought I needed to do.
I have to train harder.
While I know how to perform the dance, when it comes to Hinokami Kagura, I still haven't managed to master it.
What is it that's stopping you?
When using Hinokami Kagura with total concentration, I can't yet move my body the way I want.
But it's my own fault.
Right now, my body can't keep up.
I've improved thanks to total concentration constant.
But it's not enough.
Maintaining constant should allow me to gradually improve my stamina with each passing day.
So I won't get stronger overnight.
That day, I felt utterly weak.
I longed for there to be a way to instantly become strong enough to save Mr. Rengoku.
I tried to find one.
But no such remedy exists.
No shortcuts to be taken.
That's reality.
Even so, I'll keep moving forward.
Keep training.
No matter how grueling or frustrating things might get.
Mark my words, I will become a powerful Hashira just like Mr. Kyojiro.
That's a promise.
You know, my brother didn't have a Suguko.
Normally, I would have followed in his footsteps to become his Suguko, which would mean training as a Hashira reserve.
Unfortunately, my Nichiren sword failed to ever change its color.
I was well aware that they don't change color until you've acquired a certain level of sword skills.
Yet, no matter how much training I underwent, nothing happened.
Not everyone can be born talented.
So I'm going to forget about becoming a swordsman and find another way to be useful.
I know this will break the line of Flame Hashira and damage its long history.
But I'm sure if he were still here, then my brother would forgive me.
Walk down the path that you know to be true.
And if anyone gives you grief about it, then I'll headbutt them!
I don't think that's a good idea.
The Flame Hashira Chronicles.
I'll restore them myself.
And I'll look for other books as well.
My father might know where to look.
If anything turns up, I'll send word through our crow.
I'm glad I got to talk with you.
Thank you for coming all this way.
Oh, please.
You've got it wrong.
I should be thanking you.
Oh, there was one more thing.
Here.
Please take this.
It's my brother's Nichiren sword guard.
There's no way.
I can't accept this.
I can't.
No, I want you to have it.
Someday, I know it'll protect you.
I know it'll protect you.
I'll cherish it.
Excuse me.
Are you feeling better?
It seems our visitor left.
Shut up.
I don't give a damn.
Get out.
But what about brother's message?
It's worthless.
It's probably just his final complaints about me.
I can already guess.
Now give me some peace and quiet.
Very well, father.
Father.
Please take care of yourself.
Those are the only words you chose to leave behind for you, father.
Farewell, father.
Take care now.
Do I have a fever?
I can't breathe.
Don't worry, Nezuko.
The butterfly mansion's not too far.
You deserve nothing less than the horrible sting of 10,000 deaths.
I'm sorry.
I promise.
I'm truly sorry.
He says that he got chased by Mr. Hageneska until close to daybreak.
So that's why you're not touching your food.
More for me.
This way, quickly.
I'm sorry.
Oh, man.
If Miss Aoi hadn't calmed him down for me, he would have kept chasing me till noon.
Would anyone like seconds?
Would you like some more?
Hell yeah!
Thank you.
For yesterday.
You too, Sumi.
Kyo.
And Naho.
There's no need for thanks.
Speaking of Mr. Hageneska, what's he up to now?
Last I saw him, he was out sitting on the veranda eating rice dumplings.
And it seems like he's finally back in a good mood.
Thank goodness.
I bet you didn't know.
Rice dumplings are his favorite food in the world.
So if he's upset, he should try and buy him some.
Get me some while you're at it.
How's this?
I'll get you your own later.
Hunter!
I'm going to die!
One hundred more!
Nearly four months had gone by since Mr. Rengoku's death.
Day in and day out, we trained our very hardest.
In the meantime, we continued receiving assignments by Chrome.
All of us would take down demons whenever it was necessary.
Zenitsu would no longer throw fits, even when he had to go on solo missions.
If you give me a small lock of Nezuko's hair, I'll give it my all!
Inosuke somehow became even more of a hothead than he already was.
We better be running into our bone shatter, because I'm not settling for less!
I'm grateful, really.
You're almost there!
Come on!
That I'm not training alone.
Nezuko!
North, northwest!
Your task is to eradicate the demon that's lurking about the mountain shrine!
Nezuko, are you alright?
You getting soaked from the rain?
The demon should be around here somewhere.
North, southwest!
North, northwest!
South, northwest!
Ready?
Let's go!
South, northwest!
Damn it! I messed up!
He's headed straight toward the village!
That bastard! Who the hell does that guy think he is? Trying to take on a demon like me?
This is it. It's over for you.
Sorry about this.
I don't need your pity.
You scum!
Total concentration!
Water breathing!
Fourth form!
Striking time!
Well, that's weird. I know I heard something over here.
I'm exhausted.
Hey, we'll be reaching the Butterfly Mansion soon.
I'm exhausted. Hey, we'll be reaching the Butterfly Mansion soon.
Let me go at once!
Please, I'm begging you! Let go!
This girl is... put me down already!
Quick, you're yapping!
Damn you're loud!
Let go of her jerk!
Let go of her jerk! I can't watch this anymore!
Please, do something!
Mission, order... Shinobu...
Shinobu...
Superior...
Aoi...
Naho...
Hashira...
Coin...
Order...
I'll decide by flipping a coin.
Just follow your heart.
Kanao! Miss Kanao!
Oh, Kanao, you...
Oh, Miss Kanao!
You're not being very flashy.
Need I remind you of the orders you received?
If you're gonna be unflashy, then say something!
Ch-Change and I won!
Change and I won!
Change!
Hey, get it out! Get off me, you brats!
How dare you treat little girls like that! Let go of them, jerk!
Wait, are they swarming this guy? Or being held captive by him?
I can't tell.
He's kidnapping those girls! Hurry and rescue them!
What, you? Shut your mouth!
Are you alright?
Yes!
You're a fool!
I'm Lord Tengen Uzui, a former shinobi.
A man known around here for his resplendency.
Did you really think I'd fall for one of your vulgar headbutts?
You let those girls go!
Lousy kidnapper!
Yeah, what did you say?
You have no business doing this!
Dirty man! Dirty man! Dirty man!
Show some respect! Who do you think you're talking to?
I'm your superior! I'm your superior! I'm a Hashira, dammit!
You're a fool!
I'm Lord Tengen Uzui, a former shinobi!
Huh?
A man known around here for his resplendency.
Did you really think I'd fall for one of your vulgar headbutts?
You let those girls go! Lousy kidnapper!
Yeah, what did you say?
You have no business doing this!
Dirty man! Dirty man!
Show some respect! Who do you think you're talking to?
I'm your superior! I'm a Hashira, dammit!
Well, I don't acknowledge you as a Hashira!
Don't give me that face!
Why should I care if you don't acknowledge me?
Ya bottom feeder!
Did your brain fall out of your head or what?
I'm taking these two because I need female Corps members for a mission.
And I don't need permission to take anyone who's not a Tsuguko!
Naho isn't even a member of the Corps!
Look, she's not wearing the uniform!
Never mind.
Whoa!
What kind of brute just throws people?!
He tried me hard!
For now I'm just gonna take this one on my mission.
Not that she looks very strong.
But somehow she is a Corps member at least.
Everyone has their own personal strengths!
So don't be so insensitive and make comments like that!
Give us back Miss Aoi!
Good grief. You're really that lame.
No wonder the Demon Slayer Corps is getting weaker and weaker.
They're recruiting wimps like you who whine about everything.
What if we were to go in place of Miss Aoi?!
What do you mean, we?
Who the hell are you two?
Got something to say?
I may have just got back from training, but I've got plenty of power to spare!
I'm ready for whatever you got!
If you know what's good for you, you'll let Miss Aoi go, you hear me?!
You may be a giant muscular monster, but I'm not gonna back down!
Alright, fine. I guess I'm taking you three with me instead.
Well that didn't take much convincing.
But only if you three obey my every command!
Mr. Tanjiro?
He's huge!
Okay, so where are we going old man?
The flashiest spot in Japan that's teeming with lust and desire.
The hotbed for demons. The entertainment district.
Come out.
Thank you.
I'll go first.
I'm Tanjiro Kamuro.
I love fatia sprouts.
This is my sister Nezuko.
She adores Konpeito.
My name is Zenitsu Agatsuma, and I crave sweets all the time.
Not to mention pricey eels.
Who cares about any of that crap?
I want to know what you can do to fight off demons, not what kind of snacks you like.
The demons in the entertainment district are crazy strong.
No!
I don't want to die!
What do I do?
Just kill the demons before they kill you.
I don't want to have to fight any more demons!
I still haven't done anything with Nezuko yet!
I can't die before that!
This guy needs to shut up!
Well, I mean no gay Hashimura!
You want to hear about me, you'll have to fight me one-on-one first!
Well, now I know this guy has issues.
What'd you say?
It's the perfect time for today's Taisho-era secret!
Let me tell you a little bit more about myself.
So I was born into a clan of shinobi.
And growing up there, I led a completely unflashy life in the shadows.
Really?
No way!
Lying is bad, you know?
I'm not lying, damn it!
My pent-up anger from back then exploded, turning me into a vibrant young man!
Or, it could be I was always like this from the very start.
You all better have some flashy moves in store, you hear?
I'm picking up the scent of a strong will residing within him.
I think we can trust him.
What's with that smirk on your face, kid?
Next time, infiltrating the entertainment district!
What do you think?
Are all of you ready to go?
Yeah!
Part 2
Part 3
Part 1
Part 2
Part 3
Part 4
Part 5